Yo, this Crockett shit is really starting to piss me off.
Okay, so in case you're wondering why it appears to be this flashpoint issue right now,
it's all by design.
This is exactly what's going on, all right?
Paying attention?
Okay, this is why you're seeing this on your For You page, okay?
This issue is being propagated by the algorithm on behalf of the Democratic Party.
Their job is to put good people in a moral dilemma.
This is why you're seeing all this shit about Crockett
and why you have people running interference for her.
They're influencers that you might respect who are running interference for her.
The reason why you are seeing that is because they are being paid
to put you in a moral dilemma as a human being.
The Democrats have mastered this art for many decades now.
They offer you a choice.
You can take a position supporting a candidate
who may be pushing some decent domestic policies,
but you have to turn your back on atrocities elsewhere.
Crockett's situation, she wants you to turn your back against Palestinians
in exchange for fighting the fascism under Trump,
promising that she's going to fight Trump's fascism.
It's a false choice.
She's not going to fight Trump's fascism.
Democrats haven't been doing that at all.
So the option that you're offered either way is false.
Democrats are not going to fight Trump.
They are in bed with Trump.
They fucking love Trump.
He is built upon democratic policies.
The goal here is to force the population into a moral dilemma.
We know that you care about the Palestinians, and that's sad.
But there are bigger issues here at home.
So you're just going to need to turn your back on what's going on there.
It is a very clever, deceptive way of dividing people.
This is done in the Republican camp and the Democratic camp.
It's a great tactic.
It really is.
When you can divide people by offering them a carrot,
but they have to swallow some poison with it,
and you're hungry for a carrot,
then some people in the room will reject the carrot,
and other people will take the carrot,
and the two groups will fight over the decision.
That's what's happening here.
The carrot is a promise for some type of relief over Trump's fascism.
The poison is turning your back on Palestinians.
Very clever, and a lot of y'all are falling for it.
We need to stay evolved throughout this.
There's going to be a lot of this shit coming down the pipeline,
especially when people are emotionally and psychologically vulnerable
because of what the Trump administration is doing.
Stay sharp, fam.
As always, love you.